[一九六九年 加州帕萨迪纳市]
肖恩珊蒂娜夫人
请救救我的孩子
他连续三个晚上都听到声音
他觉得有东西在追他 快告诉她
我听到了它的声音 而且越来越响
他做过什么
- 什么都没做  - 快告诉我
他从吉普赛马车里偷了一条银项链
我们试着还回去 但他们不要
项链在哪
在这
带他进屋
不 不
No! No!
不
No!
我们马上下来
小心 胡安
胡安
Juan!
我们会再次交手的
堕入地狱
请跟着我准确地重复以下短句
Repeat the following phrases precisely as spoken.
正确的发音没有摩擦音
There is no friction with the proper diction.
要有好口音 嘴形要够圆
Good sounds abound when the mouth is round.
圆 够圆
Round. Round.
我想这个能行得通 我下午会打电话通知你们
I think we can make this work. I'll call you this afternoon and let you know.
- 非常感谢  - 谢谢
- Thank you so much.  - Thank you.
- 不客气  - 谢谢
- You're welcome.  - Thank you.
- 谢谢  - 祝您愉快
- Thank you.  - Have a great day.
- 好的 也祝您愉快  - 好的
- Yeah, you, too. Have a good day.  - Okay.
- 谢谢  - 再见
- Thank you.  - Bye.
副经理
Assistant Manager
- 杰克斯先生 这个给您  - 谢谢
- Here you go, Mr Jacks.  - Thank you.
杰克斯先生
Mr Jacks?
副经理的人选不知道您有没有决定好
I was wondering if you'd made any decision regarding the assistant manager's position.
我还在考虑 目前候选人就斯图和你
Well, I'm still deciding, and right now, it's between Stu and yourself.
斯图·鲁宾 那个新人吗
Stu Rubin, the new guy?
我知道是新人 不过他很上进 是合适人选
Well, I know he's new, but he's also quite aggressive, and we like that.
斯图不惧怕繁琐复杂的数据
You know, Stu's someone who's not afraid to crunch the numbers
还能处理棘手的问题
And make the tough decisions.
我处理棘手问题的能力也很强的
I'm perfectly capable of making the tough decisions.
人选定了我会立刻通知你 好吗
I'll let you know as soon as I decide. Okay?
这段时间 跟他讲下我们的贷款资格审核程序
In the meantime, take him through our loan qualifying procedures,
以防万一 可以吗
Just in case, all right?
知道了
Okay.
要不你先去吃午饭吧
And would you mind taking your lunch break now?
好的
Sure.
你回来的时候 记得帮我带份火鸡套餐
And maybe on your way back, you could pick me up a turkey club?
火鸡套餐 绝佳选择
Turkey club, excellent choice!
介意帮我也带一份吗 谢谢
You mind picking one up for me? Thanks.
记得加辣芥末
And spicy mustard.
- 你拿的是什么  - 您看能不能批准
- What have you got?  - Could I get your approval on this?
- 就是我们之前谈过的贷款  - 是那笔贷款啊
- This is the loan we talked about before.  - The loan.
没错
Exactly.
- 不错吧  - 一点五
- Good one, huh?  - One-point-five?
是的 而且还有很多单子
Absolutely, and it'll be one of many.
教授 恭喜第一周工作顺利
Well, Professor, congratulations on making it through your first week.
非常感谢
Thank you very much. Mmm.
- 我原以为你会留个络腮胡  - 我留了 不过有点小失望
- I thought you'd have a full beard by now.  - So did I. I'm a little disappointed.
天哪 这破烂货 我受够了
Man, this thing. That's it. I'm done. I'm out.
克莉丝 不用管它
Chris, don't even bother.
我要买台新的
I gotta get a new one.
我提醒你修这个东西你会郁闷的 已经彻底
I'm telling you, you're gonna drive yourself nuts. It's completely
坏了
Broken.
- 坏过  - 你高傲性感 还让人难以置信
- Was broken.  - You are cocky and sexy and unbelievable.
差点忘了 在银行里找到的
I almost forgot. Found it at the bank.
是什么
What is this?
不是吧 一九二九年的站立自由神像 现在几乎绝迹了
No way! Wow. It's a 1929 Standing Liberty, and it's almost fully struck.
你在银行的日常流通中发现的吗
You found this in regular circulation at the bank?
是啊
I did.
我要把它纳入自己的硬币收藏库
I'm gonna add this to my nerdy coin collection.
- 谢谢 亲爱的  - 没什么
- Thank you, baby.  - Okay.
谢谢你总是想着我
Thanks for thinking of me.
- 好了 再见  - 再见
- All right. Bye.  - Bye.
- 过会找你  - 我过会找你 好吗
- See you later.  - I'll see you later, okay?
- 道尔顿博士  - 你好 亲爱的
- Dr Dalton.  - Hello, dear.
- 你好 妈妈  - 你在干什么
-Hi, Mom.  - What are you doing?
克莉丝汀刚过来 给我带了午饭
Christine just came over and brought some lunch,
- 我在修改论文  - 克莉丝汀 那个乡下姑娘吗
- And I'm correcting some papers.  - Christine? The one from the farm?
是的 妈妈 我跟她交往快一年了
Yeah, Mom, the girl I've been dating for almost a year,
我准备和她回家吃饭 还没一起吃过饭吧
The girl who's coming for dinner. We're still on for dinner?
- 我相信她很漂亮  - 没错 我等不及要
- I'm sure she's a very sweet girl.  - She is. I can't wait for you...
但是我跟你爸都对你充满期望
But you know your father and I just have certain expectations for you
我满足不了你们的期望
I can't really do the expectations...
- 我知道艾米·库利克在找人一起打网球  - 我
- I understand Amy Kulick is looking for someone to play tennis with.  - Yeah, I...
知道吗 她以优等成绩毕业于耶鲁大学法律系
You know, she graduated from Yale Law with honours,
现在可是个很成功的律师
And she's a very successful attorney now.
- 我知道 你说起过  - 这才是我们希望
- I know. You told me.  - Yeah, that's the kind of girl
- 你在交往的女孩子  - 妈妈
- I would love to see you with.  - Mother...
她能让你平步青云
She's the kind of woman who could really help you socially
事业成功
And, as a result, in your career.
这种女孩才是你目前该考虑的对象
And that's the kind of thing you should be thinking about now.
妈妈 我不想
Mother, I don't wanna...
你不能跟个乡下姑娘鬼混
You can't be playing around with little girls off the farm.
我想你真的应该
I think you're really gonna... I think you're really gonna like...
是时候找个伴侣了
It's time to really find a partner.
克莉丝汀 我的外卖弄错了
Christine, you messed up my order.
- 不 我没弄错  - 弄错了 我说了不要蛋黄酱
- No, I didn't.  - Yeah, I said no mayo.
你没说过
You never said that.
别激动 没关系
You know what? Don't sweat it. It's okay.
杰克斯先生 你是湖人队的球迷吗
Mr Jacks, by the way, aren't you a Laker fan?
我是啊
I am a Laker fan.
我妈有周日比赛的票 我没空去
My mom is having this thing on Sunday. I can't use these.
- 真的假的  - 当然 您想看吗
- Are you serious?  - Yeah. Absolutely. You want them?
- 位子很不错啊  - 位子的确很不错
- These are great seats!  - They are great seats.
这个位子买热狗很方便
This is where they bring the hot dogs right to you.
没错 您还可以跟球星们交谈
Yes, it is. You are gonna hobnob with celebs.
- 真的让给我吗  - 当然 没关系的
- You sure that's okay?  - Absolutely, it's okay. Yeah.
- 那谢谢啦 斯图  - 您去看吧
- Well, thank you, Stu.  - Take them. Absolutely.
代我向科比问好
Say hey to Kobe for me.
一定
Of course.
你能帮帮我吗
Will you help me?
当然 我能帮您做什么吗
Of course. What can I do for you?
你们的卡车开到我家
Your trucks are at my house.
工人在打包我的家当 都是我的私人物品啊
The men are packing all my things, private things.
求求你 别让他们搬我东西
Please, make them stop.
- 您贵姓  - 加纳什
- Mrs...  - Ganush.
加纳什夫人 银行今天是通知您
Mrs Ganush, the bank is informing you of their intent
要收回您在三二五布兰登大街的房产
To repossess your property at 325 Brandon Street today.
但那是我住了三十年的家呀
But this is my home for 30 years.
在病魔夺走我眼睛之前 我都按时还贷的
And I make every payment until the sickness took my eye.
我希望能尽快筹到钱 只是需要多给点时间
I hope to have more money soon. I just need a little more time. You...
我觉得经理可能不会同意您的延期要求
I don't think my manager's going to extend you any more credit.
求求你 帮我问下
Please. Won't you try?
- 好的  - 保佑你
- Okay.  - Bless you.
保佑你
Bless you!
有一位老太太提出要延期按揭还款
We have an elderly woman asking for an extension on her mortgage payment.
她有固定收入 但之前有过医疗问题
She's on a fixed income, and she's had some medical problems.
我们应该帮帮她
There's gotta be something we can do to help her.
显然 我们已经为她延期了两次
Well, apparently, we've already granted her two extensions.
这类丧失抵押物 我们要收回固定资产
And, you know, on this type of foreclosure, we seize the trapped equity
银行要支出很大一笔费用
And the bank makes a sizable amount in fees.
我们会让她无家可归
We would have to throw her out of her house.
这是个棘手问题
It's a tough decision.
你看着办吧
Your call.
我会妥善处理的
I'll take care of it.
加纳什夫人 很抱歉
Mrs Ganush. I'm sorry, Mrs Ganush,
我们不能再提供延期还贷了
But another extension on the loan is out of the question.
- 你说什么  - 我希望能帮上忙 但是银行的规定
- What?  - I would like to help, but it is in the bank's...
不 求求你 这是我的家 以后我住哪里
No, please, this is my home. Where will I live?
您有提到您孙女 或许您可能和她一起住
You list your granddaughter as a reference. Maybe you could stay with her.
我不想给她增加负担
I would not burden her.
还有一些设施很好的老人院
And there are several fine assisted living facilities for the elderly...
疗养院吗 我可不住那些地方
A nursing home? No, I would never live in one of those places.
实在很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
我是个有自尊心的女人 布朗小姐
I am proud woman, Miss Brown,
从来没求过人
And never have I begged for anything.
但现在 我求求你
But now, I beg for you.
- 我向你跪下了  - 加纳什夫人 请别这样
- I humble myself before you.  - Mrs Ganush. Mrs Ganush, please.
- 请站起来说  - 我西尔维亚·加纳什 求求你
- Please stand up.  - I, Sylvia Ganush, beg.
以我母亲的名义 求求你
On my mother's grave, I beg you!
请松手 保安 别这样
Please let go. Let go! Security! Stop!
- 那边 比利  - 来啦
- Over here, Billy! Over here!  - We're coming.
你羞辱我
You shame me.
我求你 你却羞辱我
I beg you, and you shame me.
夫人 您的业务办理完毕了吧
I think your business is finished here, ma'am.
走吧
Let's go.
加纳什夫人
Mrs Ganush...
快出去
Get out of here!
- 过来 夫人  - 走吧
- Come on, ma'am.  - Let's go.
从没见过这样的人
I never saw anything quite like that before.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
你处理的很好
You handled that just right, you know.
- 晚安 明天见  - 好的
- Good night. See you tomorrow.  - Okay.
我刚看完这份麦克弗森的贷款
You know, I just finished going over this McPherson loan.
- 你做得不错  - 谢谢
- This is very impressive work.  - Thanks.
你能不能今晚带回去做完
Would you mind taking this home tonight and finishing it up?
因为我想明天一早就给区域副总过目
Because I would like to show it to the regional veep in the morning.
- 我很乐意  - 那太好了
- I would love to.  - Great.
谢谢
Thank you.
目前副经理的人选
And as far as that assistant manager's position goes,
你已经是首选了
You're at the top of the list.
你羞辱了我
You shamed me.
我赢啦 你个死老太婆
I beat you, you old bitch!
不
No!
女妖
Lamia.
很快 就换成你来求我了
Soon it will be you who comes begging to me.
- 她就在那  - 谢谢
- She's right over there.  - Thank you, thank you.
他们派了警察去找她谈话
Once they send some officers over to have a talk with her,
以后她就不会来烦你了 知道吗
she's not gonna be bothering you any more, okay?
你就别再想了
So don't even think about her.
我会给杰克斯先生打电话
And I'm gonna call Mr Jacks and just make sure
确保他能每晚安排保安送你上车 好吗
He can have somebody walk you to your car every night, okay?
好的
Okay.
你没事 真是谢天谢地 你没事 对吧
I just thank God you're okay. You are okay, right?
我没事
I'm fine.
怎么了 有什么事吗
What? What's the matter?
或许我应该给她办理延期还款的
It's just that maybe I could have gotten her another extension on her loan.
克莉丝 别这么做
Chris, no, don't do that.
你说过银行已经为她延期了两次 是吧
You said the bank granted this woman two extensions already, right?
那就对不起了 不按揭还款就得没收房子
I'm sorry, if you don't pay your mortgage, you lose your house.
那女人能指望什么 这不是你的错
What does this woman expect? It's not your fault.
你不必自责
You can't beat yourself up over it.
我是说那女人能指望什么 这不是你的错
I mean, what'd she expect? It's not your fault.
不管你能做或不能做
And regardless of what you may or may not have been able to do,
她都没有正当的理由
That's still no justification for her...
这是什么 怎么啦
What is it? What's wrong?
- 你听到了吗  - 听到什么
- Did you hear that?  - What?
真的吗 你没听到吗
Really? You didn't?
没有 什么声音
No. What?
我知道可能感觉会比较怪 但是我想算一卦
I know this is gonna sound weird, but I wanna get my fortune read.
现在吗 你不是开玩笑吧
Now? Are you kidding?
算了吧 克莉丝 我来帮你算吧
Come on, Chris. I'll read your fortune for you.
在不久的将来 我们一起坐车
In the near future, we are gonna get in the car,
- 然后回家放松  - 克莱 我真的很想算命
- Go home and relax.  - Clay, I really want to do this.
为什么 因为那个老女人吗
Why? Because of what happened with that old woman?
克莉丝 我想现在该送你回家了
Chris, I really think we should just get you home now.
你能陪我吗
Can you do this for me?
但愿我的学生不会看见我来
I pray to God none of my students see me here.
那样我唯一能教的班级 就只有 比如伪善一〇一
The only class I'll be able to teach is, like, Hypocrisy 101.
这里有很多选择
Yeah, there's so many things to choose from here.
不幸的是 并不是我要找的
Unfortunately, not what I'm looking for,
比如怪异的干猴子的小脑袋
Which is a weird little dried monkey head.
等等 没关系 他有一个
Wait, no, never mind, he's got one.
我叫拉姆·加斯 是个预言者
I am Rham Jas, seer.
- 我叫克莉丝汀 这位是克莱  - 或许你已经知道了 是吧
- I'm Christine and this is Clay. -But you probably already knew that, right?
- 开个玩笑  - 我能帮你什么忙吗
- Just kidding. -How can I help you?
我想占卜一下自己的命运 可以吗
I would like to have my fortune read. Can you do that?
我能看到某些能量
I have the ability to see certain energies.
有时 这些能量就是事物的前兆
Sometimes these energies are a foretoken of things to come.
请支付六十美元
$60, please.
- 真的假的  - 当然
- Seriously?  - Yes.
六十美元 这个开价是不是太高了
Sixty... Doesn't that seem a little steep for this sort of thing?
- 如果你不是诚心诚意 请回吧  - 那好 走吧 克莉丝
- If you're not serious, please go. -All right. Come on, Chris.
等等 我来付吧
Wait, wait! I'll... I'll pay.
不用 我来付吧
No, you know what? You know what? I got it. I got it.
- 给  - 白金卡 不错
- There you go.  - Platinum card. Very good.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 过来 亲爱的  - 谢谢
-Here, here, baby. -Thanks.
应该的
Sure.
那边请
Uh-uh. Please.
好的
Okay.
你想了解自己的命运
So, you wish to know something of your destiny.
- 是的  - 非常好
- Yes.  - Very good.
来看看店里的天意
Let's see what the fates have in store.
弗洛伊德曾说命运并不是天意的表现
You know, Freud said destiny was not an act of fate,
而是由我们潜意识产生
But rather something created by our subconscious
并控制我们有意识的选择
To control our conscious choices.
没错 不过我们不能单凭智力去认知世界
That's true. But we cannot attempt to understand the world by intellect alone.
- 卡尔·荣格  - 是的
- Carl Jung.  - Yes.
出自他的论文 心理学形态
From his treatise Psychological Types.
- 那么  - 荣格 新时代人们最喜爱的心理学家
- So...  - Jung, the New Agers' favourite psychologist.
因为他不怕把上帝拿到公式里讲
Because he wasn't afraid to bring God into the equation.
他不怕把上帝拿到…
Well, he wasn't afraid to bring God into...
- 克莱 别说了  - 好的 我知道 开始吧
- Clay, Clay, come on.  - Let's do it. I know. Come on. Let's start.
- 可以开始了吗  - 我已经准备好了
- Shall we?  - I'm ready.
很好 请把你的手给我
Very well. Please, give me your hand.
好的
Okay.
这样放 好的
This way. Okay.
你的工作和钱有关
You work with money.
没错
That's right.
最近你丢了东西
And you've recently lost something.
- 好像没有  - 不 不 你还没丢
- No, I don't think so.  - No. No, you haven't lost anything.
但是你有东西被人拿走
But something's been taken from you.
没有
No.
- 一粒钮扣  - 天哪 是的
- A button.  - Oh, my God. Yes!
谁都看得出她少了粒钮扣 那又怎样
Well, anyone can see she's missing a button! So what?
但是 克莱 这的确很奇怪
But, Clay, it was really strange.
今天那个老女人 从我袖子上拿走了一粒钮扣
The old woman today, she took a button from my sleeve.
- 她为什么要这么做  - 你们两个能不能安静点
- Why would she do that?  - If you would both please just be quiet!
- 我想今晚差不多了  - 怎么啦
- I think that's enough for tonight.  - What's wrong?
我很累了 而且天色已晚
I'm tired, and I see it's become quite late.
当然 我会退钱给你
I will, of course, refund your money.
等等 你看到了什么吗
Wait, wait, wait! Did you see something?
一个恶灵缠上你了
A dark spirit has come upon you.
- 什么意思  - 他的意思是…
- What do you mean?  - Well, he's...
你有去墓地亵渎死者吗
Did you blaspheme the dead while visiting a graveyard?
- 没有  - 你玩过占卜盘吗
- No!  - Did you play with a Ouija board
或者和练习黑暗魔法的人有交往
Or consort with those who practise the black arts?
好了 别紧张 拜托
All right, take it easy, man. Come on.
等等 克莱 我都没有做过
Wait. Clay, Clay, Clay. No. No, I didn't.
或许有人对你下了诅咒
Perhaps someone has cursed you.
那他怎么会知道那些
Then how did he know all that?
知道什么 你丢了钮扣吗
Know what? That you lost a button?
再说了 他并不是很了解
And by the way, he didn't really know that much.
他做了一些可能的猜测 然后
He makes a couple of good guesses, then he...
他说动你 然后给你一堆的问题
He stirs you up, and then he leaves you with all these questions
然后顺手递上自己的名片
And, conveniently, his business card.
克莉丝 他只是个江湖骗子
Come on, Chris, he's a scam artist.
但是他没有要钱啊 他想退给我们 记得吗
But he didn't want the money. He tried to give it back, remember?
其实他在装 最后还不是收了 是吧
Well, he sort of tried, but in the end, he took it, didn't he?
可能吧
I guess so.
我要去找拖你车的人
I gotta go meet the guy that's towing your car,
你会没事吧
So you gonna be okay?
- 是的  - 那就好 猫咪要好好照顾她哦
- Yeah.  - All right. Kitty, take care of her.
- 一小时后见 我爱你  - 好的
- I'll see you in about an hour. Love you.  - Okay.
好的
Okay.
- 给 放在嘴唇上  - 谢谢
- Here. Put that on your lip.  - Thank you.
真不敢相信她竟然到家里来了
I can't believe she came to the house.
这太疯狂了 我要报警
This is so nuts. I'm calling the cops.
- 不是她干的  - 那会是谁
- It wasn't her.  - Who was it then?
我不知道 看不清是什么
I don't know. I couldn't see who it was.
一定是她 肯定是她
Of course it was her. It had to be her.
不要 克莱 谁都不是
No, Clay, it wasn't anyone!
肯定是某个人 克莉丝 一定是某个人
It was somebody. Chris, it had to be somebody.
灯灭了 你看不清楚是谁罢了
The lights were out. You just couldn't see who it was,
- 但我猜是  - 克莱 当时根本没人
- But I'm guessing it was...  - Clay, there wasn't anybody here.
那会是谁干的
Then who did this?
谁打你的脸了
Who hit you in the face?
我认为是今天早前受袭击的一个反应
I think it's just a reaction to her being attacked earlier in the day.
是的 外伤后压力的典型症状
Yeah. Classic symptoms of post-traumatic stress.
是的 她有恐慌和惊吓症状 所以…
Yeah, she's showing signs of panic and paranoia. so...
不 不 不 我没事
No, no, no, I'll be fine.
好的
All right.
嗨 嗨
Hey, hey.
现在感觉怎么样了
How you doing?
- 好多了  - 是吗
-Better. -Yeah?
多亏医生的开导
Especially after the doctor explained it to me.
他说在暴力受害者身上
He said that victims of violence,
- 偶尔会发生…- 发生悲剧再现
- They re-experience...  - Re-experience their trauma.
我错以为是什么更严重的事
I misinterpreted it to be something more than it was.
- 碰巧罢了  - 我只是…感觉…
- Happens.  - I just... I feel...
- 怎么了  - 有点难堪
- What?  - Kind of embarrassed.
别开玩笑了
Are you kidding?
跟我在一块儿还有什么好难堪的
No. You never have to be embarrassed with me.
记住了
Okay?
嗨 要不周六出去旅旅游散散心 怎么样
Hey, listen, I was thinking maybe we could take a little trip on Saturday,
- 坐火车去圣巴巴拉  - 你的乡村木屋
- Get on the train and go to Santa barbara.  - Your folks' cabin.
是啊 如果你想去
Yeah, if you're up for it, the cabin.
- 天呢 我当然愿意去  - 真的 好极了
- Oh, my god, I would love to!  - Yeah? Good.
- 真是太开心了  - 宝贝 你肯定喜欢的
- That'd be so exciting.  - Baby, you're gonna love it.
- 你肯定喜欢的  - 好的
- You're gonna love it.  - Okay, good.
我一直打算让你去瞧瞧呢
I'm excited for you to see it.
- 那些树 还都是私人的  - 那真是太好了
- These trees and it's private.  - That would be great.
肯定会很好玩
It'll be great. It'll be good.
我们可以可以… 我们可以聊天什么的
I think we need to. and we can just... We can just talk and stuff.
怎么了
What?
- 怎么了  - 我有点…有点头昏脑胀
- What's the matter?  - I couldn't... I couldn't wake up.
没事的 过来 那只是一个梦罢了
It's okay. Okay. Come here. It was just a dream.
宝贝 租的车停在那边
Baby, that's the rental car they dropped off this morning.
- 知道了吗 好的  - 谢谢
- Okay? Sure. -Thanks.
- 我爱你  - 我也爱你
- Love you.  - Love you, too.
嗨 宝贝 今天记着别再惹老女人了
Hey, baby, try not to piss off any old ladies today, okay?
海 克莉丝汀
Hey, Christine?
- 什么事 你刚来吗  - 怎么了 你又不是考勤员
- What, are you just getting here?  - What are you, the hall monitor?
克莉丝汀 你太幽默了
Ha, ha. Very funny, Christine.
这是什么
What's this?
你要干嘛
What do you want?
我想让你再教教我关于贷款手续
I need you to finish teaching me the loan procedures.
我现在有点心烦 能不能明天着
I've got a lot on my mind. Can we do this tomorrow?
- 当然  - 好的
- Sure.  - Okay.
我就告诉杰克斯先生你现在没空就是了
I'll just tell Mr Jacks that you don't have the time right now.
- 也许他可以告诉我  - 不 不 我来吧
- Maybe he can tell me.  - No, no! Okay, I'll do it.
好的
Okay.
我们之前看到抵押贷款须知
We were going over the asset-based lending guidelines.
是
Right.
我们假设你的客户是一家公司
Let's say your client is a company
但通过传统方式得不到银行资助
That can't get traditional bank financing.
- 并且  - 并且…
- And?  - And...
并且
And?
并且…
And...
并把你肮脏丑陋的爪子从我桌子上拿开
And get your filthy pig knuckle off my desk!
克莉丝汀 你流血了…布朗
Christine blood... Brown.
克莉丝汀 你的鼻子
Christine. Your nose.
当然 你能等会吗
Sure, can you hold?
- 我来帮你  - 不用 不用 我自己能行
- Let me help you.  - No, no, I've got it under control.
天啊 天啊
Oh, my god! Oh, my god!
天啊 天啊 把它止住
God! Oh, my god! Stop it!
杰克斯先生
Mr Jacks!
- 有没有溅到我嘴里  - 天啊
- Did I get any in my mouth?  - Oh, my god!
有没有溅到我嘴里
Did I get any in my mouth?
我带您到那边清理一下吧
Let me take you over here to get clean.
实在对不起 天啊
I'm so sorry! Oh, my god!
只是流鼻血
It's just a nosebleed.
- 我嘴里有没有  - 我们会给您清理消毒
- Did I get any in my mouth?  - We'll clean you up. We have antiseptic.
有事吗
What is it?
你好 我来找西尔维亚·加纳什 她在吗
Hi. I came to see Sylvia ganush. Is she here?
你是谁
Who are you?
我是她的一个朋友
I'm a friend of hers.
- 一个…  - 等一下
- Someone...  - Wait.
我知道你是谁了 奶奶告诉过我你会来
I know who you are. Grandma told me you would come.
你就是银行那个夺走她房子的
You are the woman from the bank, the one who took her house.
事实上 是银行拿走了房子
Actually, it was the bank that took the house.
我是说 我只负责在那工作
I mean, I just work there.
事实上 我曾试着帮你奶奶拿回房子
In fact, I tried to help your grandma get the house back,
但老板就是不同意
But my boss wouldn't let me.
你就这样站在我门口跟我撒谎
Are you going to stand here on my porch and lie to my face?
- 没有  - 你以前很胖 是不是
- No.  - You used to be a real fat girl, didn't you?
- 是的  - 我能看出来
- Yeah.  - I can tell.
我们不欢迎你来这
You are not welcome here.
等等 我想见见她
Wait! wait. I need to see her.
我想她能原谅我 我会把她的房子弄回来的
I need her to forgive me. And I'll get her the house back.
你会帮她摆平一切 是吗
And you are gonna make everything all right for her, is that it?
是的
Yes.
进来吧
Come on.
她在哪
Where is she?
- 把她移开 把她移开  - 快 别看
- Get her off me! Get her off me!  - Come! Don't look.
- 抓住她的肩膀  - 用点力 把她举起来
- Grab her shoulder.  - Be a man! Lift her up!
- 小心点  - 来掷骰子吧
- Be careful.  - Let's roll the dice!
还要帮她摆平吗
Still going to make everything all right for her?
你活该
You deserve everything that is coming to you.
- 再来一次
- One more time!
我相信折磨你的是个女妖
I believe what plagues you is the lamia.
女妖 那个老女人就是这么喊的
Lamia, that's the word the old woman used.
这个恶魔 只听吉普赛人的召唤做坏事
The black goat, only summoned by gypsies for their darkest deeds.
头三天
For the first three days,
女妖以凶灵的形象出现 慢慢折磨你
The lamia appears as a nasty spirit that torments its victim.
然后 她会把你的灵魂带走
After that, it reveals itself to be a taker of souls,
她会来找那个被诅咒物的所有者
And it comes for the owner of the accursed object.
被诅咒物 什么东西
Accursed object. What object?
从受害者身上拿的东西 下咒后 又还回的
Something taken from the victim, cursed and given back.
这个
This?
我把它烧了呢
What if I just burn it?
不管这个扣子怎么样
I'm afraid no matter what condition the button is in,
你还是所有者 女妖同样会来带你走
You would still be the owner. The lamia would still come to take you.
带我去哪
Take me where?
- 我怎么才能避免  - 你可以试着安抚她
- Then how do I get rid of this?  - You could attempt to appease the spirit.
最简单的方式就是供奉血淋淋的祭品
The simplest way would be a blood offering.
可以用一些小动物 或者鸡也行
A small creature could be sacrificed, a chicken perhaps.
不行 听着 我是一个素食主义者
No way! Look, I'm a vegetarian.
天呢 我还在动物保护所当志愿者
I volunteer at the puppy shelter, for christ's sake.
我是不会杀生的
I don't go around killing animals.
到时候你就知道你会不会了
You will be surprised what you'll be willing to do
当女妖找上门时
When the lamia comes for you.
这本书可以教你怎么做
This will show you how.
过来 猫咪 猫咪
Here, kitty, kitty.
克莉丝 克莉丝
Chris! Chris?
克莉丝
Chris?
嗨 你在这啊 你在这干嘛呢
Hey, there you are. What are you doing out here?
宝贝 我打电话到银行 他们说你早走了
Baby, I called the bank. They said you left early.
你也没接我电话 那是血吗
You're not answering my calls. Is that blood?
不是 怎么会有血呢
No. why would there be blood?
是啊 宝贝 那…那有血 在你袖子上
Yeah, baby, there's... there's blood on your sleeve.
- 你在流血吗  - 没有
- Are you bleeding?  - No.
那只是番茄汁
It was just tomato juice.
我刚才在切番茄
I was cutting a tomato in the
可能一不小心溅上来了
Kitchen and it must have gotten on my sleeve.
克莉丝 要不我们改天吃晚饭吧
Hey, chris, why don't we do this dinner another time?
你这几天过的太难了 我觉得是最好还是
You've had a rough couple of days. I think it's better.
没事 我想去
No, I want to go to the dinner.
我知道 但是你确定你没事吗
I know, but are you sure you're feeling all right?
说实话 过去几天确实不顺
Honestly, I haven't been.
但是我觉得…
But I think...
我现在觉得一切都好了
I think that everything is gonna be okay now.
真的
I really do.
怎么样
What do you think?
你看起来太漂亮了
You look beautiful.
真的 天啊
It really is. My god.
里面也很漂亮
It's gonna be nice inside, too.
他们会喜欢你的
They're gonna love you.
- 克莱顿  - 妈妈
- Clayton.  - Hello, mother.
见到你真高兴 这是克莉丝汀
Good to see you. This is Christine.
- 这是我母亲 特鲁迪  - 你好 克莉丝汀
- That's my mom, Trudy.  - Hello, Christine.
你好 很高心见到你
Hello. It's very nice to meet you.
- 哦  - 请进 请进
- Well.  - Please, come in. Come in.
好
Yes.
- 老爸 最近过的怎么样  - 嗨 儿子
- Hey, Dad, how are you?  - Hey, son.
伯父 很高兴见到您
Good to see you, sir.
这是克莉丝汀 这是我爸爸 莱昂纳德
This is Christine. Christine, this is my dad, Leonard.
- 你好  - 嗨 玛丽娅 谢谢
- Nice to meet you.  - Hi, Maria. Thank you.
- 你们家真漂亮  - 谢谢
- You have a beautiful home.  - Well, thank you very much.
- 你要不要喝点什么  - 要酒吗？
- Can I get you a drink?  - Yeah, wine?
- 你们要吗  - 当然
- Do you guys want?  - Sure.
- 好的 过来帮我  - 我一会回来
- Okay. Come help me.  - I'll be right back.
好的 亲爱的
Yes, dear.
- 希望你不要太介意  - 太客气了
- I hope you don't mind.  - How thoughtful.
- 自己做的  - 是的
- Homemade?  - Yes.
你们管这种蛋糕叫什么
And what type of cake would you call that?
我们叫它
It's called
丰收蛋糕
A harvest cake.
你们是不是在农场上经常做啊
Is that something you would make on a farm?
不
No.
现在不了 我们过去还有一群鹅时常做
I mean, not any more. We used to when we had a gaggle of geese.
- 鹅？  - 就是在快到收获季节的时候
- Geese?  - Well, right around the harvest time,
也就是下鹅蛋时
That's when your goose eggs will make a real dense yolk.
鹅蛋黄可以用来做大蛋糕
It makes for a rich cake.
哦 非常感谢
Well, just thank you.
- 我们来了  - 对不起打断你们的谈话
- Here we are.  - Sorry to interrupt the bonding sesh.
- 到宴厅来吧  - 好的
- Why don't you join us in the dining room?  - Good.
- 好 我们走 就在那边  - 好的
- Yeah, let's go. It's right in here.  - Okay.
- 天啊  - 赫库巴
- Jeez.  - Hecuba.
我从来就不了解那只该死的猫 我讨厌猫
I never did understand that damned animal. I hate cats.
真奇怪 赫库巴通常很乖的
That is so strange. Hecuba is usually very sweet.
没关系 我也曾有只猫 我能理解
That's okay. I had a cat. I understand.
你是说…你是说你现在养的那只猫吧
You mean... you mean you have a cat.
什么意思 那只猫怎么了
What do you mean? Did something happen?
是不是发生什么事了
Unless something happened to him.
我怎么会知道呢
Well, how am I supposed to know?
我是说 你也知道 猫总喜欢跑来跑去
I mean, you know how cats are. They come and they go.
是啊
That's true.
- 你要不要…  - 哦…是的 谢谢
- Well, should...  - Well... yes. Yes, please.
儿子 古币收集的怎么样了
So, how's the coin collection, son?
我老爸通常会问"你还是个收集狂"
That's my dad's way of saying, "so, you're still a huge nerd?"
还好 事实上 克莉丝汀刚刚给我了一个
It's good. It's good. In fact, Christine just got me
一九二九年纪念自由女神站立像的硬币呢
A 1929 standing liberty quarter at her bank.
- 真的吗  - 太不可思议了吧 那硬币很少见
- Really?  - Isn't that crazy? Yeah, it's rare.
我猜当一名银行出纳员肯定很难了
I just think the job of a bank teller must be so difficult,
天天计算 重复 肯定很烦人
With all that counting and repetition. It must get very tedious.
是的 你说的对
Yes, you're right,
- 但我不是出纳员  - 哦
- But I'm not a teller.  - Oh?
是啊 妈妈 我告诉过你 克莉丝汀是放贷人
Yeah, mom, I told you. Christine's a loan officer.
她们银行所有小型经商和家庭贷款都归她管
She handles all the loans for small businesses and homes for her bank.
而且她最近要提升了 所以…对吗 克莉丝
And she's up for this big promotion, so... right, Chris?
如果我能把手头处理的一笔贷款业务结清了
If I could close this one account that I'm working on,
说不定就可以得到提拔了
It would really help.
那笔贷款肯定很重要
That must be a very important loan.
是啊 那是我们银行处理过的最大数目的
It's the biggest that my branch has ever handled.
你怎么接手这笔贷款的
And how did that come to you?
哦 我当时在读华尔街报
Well, I was reading the wall street journal
看到这家药材供应公司
And came across this medical supply company
打算扩张 但是没有足够的流动资金
That was looking to expand but didn't have the liquidity.
所以我就去见了他们总裁 提出了一套方案
So I met with their CEO and presented a formula
来帮助他们申请长期贷款
For restructuring some of their long-term debt.
克莉丝汀 看来你做的不错啊
Sounds like you've got a lot going for you, Christine.
你母亲肯定会为你感到自豪
Well, your mother must be very proud of you.
可能吧
I suppose.
我不太经常跟我妈妈见面
I don't see much of my mother.
- 为什么  - 哦 妈妈 那…那是人家的私事
- Why is that?  - Wow, mom, that's... it's kind of personal.
我在跟克莉丝汀说话
I'm speaking to Christine.
自从我爸爸去世后 她就不怎么爱说话了
Well, ever since my dad died, she doesn't talk much.
一直待在农场上 自娱自乐 沉醉于…
She just stays on the farm and keeps to herself because...
沉醉于什么
Because?
因为她丈夫去世了 妈妈 所以她想一个人过
Because her husband died, mom, and she just wants to be by herself.
- 为什么不…  - 因为我妈妈嗜酒如命
- Why don't...  - Because my mother's an alcoholic.
哦
Oh.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这也不是什么丢人的事
It's certainly nothing to be ashamed of.
反而我觉得 你的诚实很令人佩服
I have to say, I find your honesty very refreshing.
我父亲曾经也是经常酗酒
My father had a drinking problem,
但我从来都不敢承认
And I was always too ashamed to admit it.
你比较有勇气
You've got backbone.
不像上次他带回来的那个女孩
Unlike that last girl he brought by.
- 她叫什么来着  - 艾丽丝
- What was her name?  - Alice.
- 我们没必要…  - 艾丽莎
- We don't have to...  - Alicia!
- 艾丽莎  - 克莉丝汀 你不知道 那个女生太可怕了
- Alicia.  - She was dreadful, Christine.
显得有点病怏怏的 而且一点理想都没有
She was ill-mannered, no ambition at all.
那其实不太算是…  - 他们是在网上认识的
That's not really...  - They met on the internet.
那是什么
What is that,
你不知道
Really?
- 什么意思  - 我对他太严厉了吗
- What does that mean?  - Am I being too hard on him?
没有 一点都不会
No, not at all.
谢谢
Thanks a lot...
我觉得我应该尝尝你们带来的蛋糕
You know, I think I will try some of that cake of yours.
看啊 看起来真不错
Look at that. It looks great.
看起来很有趣
It looks so interesting.
你如果不喜欢 就只能说你有审美问题
You only dislike it if you hate delicious things.
不是我的问题
Not my problem.
真可爱
Lovely.
谢谢你 克莉丝汀 太棒了
Thank you, Christine. This is wonderful.
而且刚好用来转移话题
It also changed the subject nicely.
谢谢 看起来很好吃
Thank you. That looks good!
是啊
That's right.
这真的做的很精致 是不是
It sounds so quaint, doesn't it?
你有没有听到什么动静啊
Did you hear something?
没有 你还好吧
No. You okay?
真好吃
Tasty!
- 我很喜欢  - 我确实喜欢
- I like it a lot.  - I do like it.
妈妈 刚才你说我们是在网上认识的
You know, mom, when you say we met on the internet,
可能容易让人误解
It's a little misleading.
当然为了找个好伴侣那样做也无可厚非
Yes, well you need to do that to find a good mate.
但是你不能相信
You can't even trust
诸如你听到的或者别人写在网上的自我介绍
The things you hear or that people write about themselves.
- 很好  - 甚至连照片多数都是假的
- Very nice.  - Even the pictures are false half the time.
这是真的
It's true.
我不觉得这算是一种误解
I don't think it's a misconception
那些有良好教养
To think that people of good breeding
并且成功的人应该
And success should be able to meet
在现实生活中寻找人生伴侣
Potential life partners in a realistic situation.
还有 别老是逛酒吧
Well, you also have a thing about bars.
你经常去吗 克莉丝汀
Would you, Christine?
- 不 当然不去  - 什么 但我们去的啊
- No, no, of course not.  - What? What... but we did.
克莉丝 我们是在酒吧认识的啊 你怎么了
We met at a bar, Chris. What are you talking about?
她…
She...
那不是三K党聚会的地方 妈妈 就是个酒吧
It's not a klan rally, mom. It's a bar.
对 我们 我们在酒吧邂逅
Yeah, we met... we met at a bar,
从网上联系开始约会的
And we set up the date on the internet.
你没事吧
You okay? You okay?
喝点水 宝贝 喝点… 噎着了
Some water? Baby, have some... went down the wrong pipe.
天呢
Oh, my god!
对不起 我没有… 是不是有窗户开着
I'm sorry, I don't... there must be a window open.
克莉丝
Chris?
见鬼 我能听见你
Okay, I hear you!
你在地狱吗  - 离我远点
What in the hell?  - Leave me alone.
- 听见吗 离我远点  - 克莉丝 别这样
- Just leave me the hell alone!  - Hey! Hey! Chris! Stop it!
宝贝 那里没人
Baby! There's no one there.
好吧
Okay.
- 我觉得我应该走了  - 是啊 我觉得也是
- I think I'd better go.  - Yes, I think that would be best.
我知道 等一下 克莉丝…
I know. Wait, Chris...
别跟着她 那个女孩有病
Don't follow her! She's a sick girl.
- 妈妈 她需要帮助  - 让她走吧
- Mom, she needs my help.  - Let her go.
等等
Wait!
怎么了
What's the matter?
听着 我听你的杀了那只猫
Look, I did what you said! I killed that little kitty!
你满嘴胡话
You're so full of shit!
你要知道我们面对是一股强大的黑暗势力
These are elusive and powerful forces we are dealing with.
没有任何保证能一定成功
There are no guarantees.
我们必须直接跟这恶灵谈话
We must speak directly to this dark spirit.
我们必须劝止她抓走你的灵魂 尽快
We must dissuade it from taking your soul, and soon.
- 我知道有人可以帮我们  - 我该不该相信你
- I know someone who can help us.  - And I'm supposed to trust you?
明天就是第三天了 之后 女妖就来抓你了
Tomorrow is the third day. After that, the lamia will come for you.
我们不能让她得逞 但你必须要明白
We can't let that happen. But you must understand,
帮我们的那个女人 自己也会身陷绝境
The woman who can help us must put herself at great risk.
- 她是不会免费为你做的  - 你想我怎样
- She will not do that for free.  - What do you need from me?
一万美金
$10,000 cash
明天前准备好
By tomorrow.
- 杰克斯先生  - 什么事
- Mr Jacks.  - Yeah?
问这挺难为情的 我知道正式任命还没下来
This is kind of awkward for me, and I know it's not official yet,
但我能不能预支我新职位的薪资
But I was wondering if I could get an advance for the new position.
副经理的职位吗
What, the assistant manager's position?
对 我有位家庭成员病得很厉害
Yes. See, one of my family members is really sick.
- 他们虽不至于死 但也很危险  - 克莉丝汀
- They're not gonna die, but they could.  - Christine. Christine.
出了件事 麦克弗森那买卖昨晚被取消了
There's a problem. The Mcpherson deal was cancelled last night.
- 什么  - 对
- What?  - Yeah.
我跟区域办公室刚说完
Right after I informed the regional
我们有一笔大贷款项目
Office that we had this big loan pending,
我就发现他们跟我们的对手成交了
I find out that they just made their deal over at first national.
现在 我要找人来问问怎么回事
Now, I gotta call in to see what exactly happened,
目前为止 这事对你对我来说都不太好
But right now, this does not look too good for you or for me.
所以 副经理的职位先放一放
So, this assistant manager promotion has been delayed.
说实话 就目前发生的每件事
In fact, you know, I think, with everything that's been happening,
我想得把这份工作交给斯图
I think I'm gonna have to give this job to Stu.
斯图 我明白了
Stu. I see.
很抱歉 若是家里出了问题
I'm sorry. Look, if you've got family problems,
或许你该请几天假 解决之后…
Maybe you should take the day off, sort them out and...
[当铺]
- 多少钱  - 总共三千八百元
- So, how much?  - $3,800 for everything.
- 我的首饰算了吗  - 算了
- Including my jewellery?  - Including.
这些东西肯定不止这个价
But this Stuff is worth so much more than that.
拜托 这是我的全部财产 我求求你
Please. This is all I have. I'm begging you.
要不要随你的便
Take it or leave it.
克莉丝 克莉丝
Chris? Chris?
宝贝
Baby?
我以为你有乳糖不耐症
I thought you were lactose intolerant.
对
I am.
不过我想 管他呢 我就要吃冰激凌
But then I thought, "screw it, I'm eating ice cream."
我把钱给拉姆·加斯了
I paid Rham Jas.
什么 没开玩笑吧
What? You're kidding me.
我付钱给他
I paid him.
为什么 我以为你不信那个的
Why? I mean, I thought that you didn't believe.
我也不知道什么该信什么不该信
I don't know what I believe in any more.
我不信 但我知道你信
I really don't, but I know that you believe in this.
而且这对你来说很重要
I know how important it is to you,
为这你遭了很大的罪
And I know how much pain this is causing you.
我还记得
And, I also remembered...
我爱上你的那个晚上
I remembered a promise that I made
我曾做出承诺
The night I fell in love with you.
我跟自己说
I told myself that I would...
我会一辈子呵护你 照顾你
I would always look out for you. I'd always take care of you.
所以我付钱给他了
So I paid him.
你还记得爱上我的那个晚上
You remember the night that you fell in love with me?
第二个晚上也记得呢
I remember the second I fell in love with you.
天呀
Oh, my god.
确定不用我跟你进去吗
You sure you don't want me to go in with you?
他说我要独自面对
He said I should come alone.
我知道 他也跟我说了
Yeah, I know, I know he did. He told me the same thing.
克莉丝汀
Christine, if you will permit me
请允许我介绍 肖恩珊蒂娜
The pleasure of an introduction, Shaun San Dena.
- 幸会  - 你好吗
- Welcome.  - How do you do?
肖恩珊蒂娜是经验丰富的灵媒师
Shaun San Denais an experienced medium.
并且 她曾与那个女妖打过交道
Furthermore, she's personally been touched by the Lamia.
多年前 就在这间屋子里我见过它
I first encountered this spirit many years ago in this very house.
当时是怎么回事
And what happened?
一个男孩的灵魂被它抢走了
I lost a young boy's soul to the beast.
我苦守了这么多年
I have waited these long years
等待时机救赎自己
For a chance at redeeming myself,
斩妖除魔
A chance to destroy the foul thing.
今晚 我的机会来了
Tonight, my chance will come.
我需要你来引诱她
But to summon it, I will need your help.
你敢吗
Can you be strong?
我试试
I'll try.
我前夫桑德尔 也是灵媒师
My late husband, Sandor, was also medium.
他把房子建在这儿
He chose this site to build a house upon
因为他认为这地方存在某种力量
Because he sensed certain forces at work here.
这地方 有种特殊的…
In this place, there is a particular...
一种特殊的能量结界
A particular confluence of forces
可以打开一扇门
Which allows a doorway to be opened through which we may pass...
阳间与阴间的通道
...and through which others may pass into our world.
请坐
Please be seated.
怎么回事
What's going on?
我们做的每件事都是为你好
Everything we're doing is for your own good.
没事的 克莉丝汀 请坐
Please. Christine, please.
谢谢
Thank you.
我被魂灵附体时 把我的手放在羊身上
Once the spirit has entered me, put my hand upon the animal.
- 明白吗  - 好
- Do you understand?  - Yes.
我会把女妖魂灵逼到山羊身上
I force the spirit of the Lamia into the goat.
米洛斯 到时候出剑
Milos, that's when you strike.
明白
I understand.
大家都要请灵
We all must be receptive.
- 我该做些什么  - 你得让黑暗进来
- What am I supposed to do?  - You must allow the darkness in.
引导幽灵进入自己的灵魂里
You must invite the dead to co-mingle with your spirit.
- 我很怕  - 是的
- I'm scared.  - Yes.
重复这句话 迎接死灵至吾魂魄
Now repeat these words, "I welcome the dead into my soul."
- 迎接死灵至吾魂魄  - 一定要虔诚
- I welcome the dead into my soul.  - You must believe it!
迎接死灵至吾魂魄
I welcome the dead into my soul.
- 迎接死灵至吾魂魄  - 迎接死灵至吾魂魄
- I welcome the dead into my soul.  - I welcome the dead into my soul.
- 迎接死灵至吾魂魄  - 至吾魂魄
- I welcome the dead into my soul.  - ...into my soul.
迎接死灵至吾魂魄 迎接死灵至吾魂魄
I welcome the dead into my soul. I welcome the dead into my soul.
迎接死灵至吾魂魄
I welcome the dead into my soul.
迎接死灵至…
I welcome the dead...
迎接死灵至吾魂魄
I welcome the dead into my soul.
迎接死灵至吾…
I welcome the dead into...
周围有其他魂魄
Something else is here with us.
是的
Yes.
不是女妖
This is not the Lamia.
是一些…
It is the spirit of some
多年不得超生的怨灵
Unsettled soul from years ago.
有时这些游魂会在门周围游荡
Sometimes the unsettled ones linger by the door.
还有其它的魂魄
There are others here, as well.
走开 愚蠢的野鬼 走开
Begone, foolish spirits! Begone!
她来了
She is coming.
肖恩珊蒂娜里面是谁
Who now inhabits the body of Shaun San Dena?
女妖
Lamia!
女妖 你渴求什么
Lamia, what is it you desire?
我渴求克莉丝汀的灵魂
I desire the soul of Christine Brown!
就等她一进坟墓 我们就把她吃光
We will feast upon it as she festers in the grave!
不是我干的 是我们经理吉姆·杰克斯
No! It was my manager, Jim Jacks!
- 他才是 他…- 闭嘴
- He was the one! He was...  - Silence!
女妖 你肯定能放弃这位无关紧要的灵魂
Lamia, surely you can be dissuaded from taking this insignificant woman.
她肯定不值得你大费周章
Surely she is not worthy of your greatness.
不
No!
我为你来的 克莉丝汀
I come for you, Christine.
你是我的
You're mine!
不
No!
你阴我 邪恶的贱人
You tricked me! You black-hearted whore!
- 米洛斯 快  - 婊子
- Now, Milos, now!  - You bitch.
走开 不洁的灵魂
Away, unclean spirit.
女妖
Lamia!
吾 唤汝入人间者
As one who summoned you to this circle,
命令汝即退人间
I command you to leave this instant.
克莉丝汀
Christine!
我不稀罕你的猫 你这臭婊子
I don't want your cat, you dirty pork queen!
肖恩珊蒂娜
Shaun san dena!
驱赶恶灵
You must banish the spirit!
好
Yes!
米洛斯
Milos!
- 我的天 我还好  - 谢天谢地
- Oh, my god. I'm okay.  - Thank god!
- 还活着  - 难以置信
- I'm okay.  - Unbelievable!
- 你做到了  - 谢天谢地
- You did it!  - Thank god.
我尽力了
I tried.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
天呢 帮帮忙
Oh, my god. Help me!
叫救护车
Call an ambulance.
她有气吗
Is she breathing?
没
No.
天呢
Oh, my gosh.
- 太让人伤心了  - 是的
- It's so sad.  - Yes.
怎么会这样
Strange how things work out.
她等了四十年 就为除掉女妖
She waited 40 years for another chance to overcome the Lamia,
最后 生前最后一晚 她成功了
And finally, on the last night of her life, she did.
不 恐怕你搞错了
No, I'm afraid you misunderstand.
灵媒师是消灭不了女妖的
The Lamia cannot be banished by a medium.
今晚失败了 抱歉
This is our lesson tonight. I'm sorry.
- 但我看见她除掉那家伙了  - 没有
- But I saw her get rid of the thing.  - No.
它不过是被驱赶走了
You saw her drive it. That is all.
它还会回来的 山羊从没被斩尽杀绝的
It will be back. The goat was never slaughtered.
今晚一过
When this night is through,
女妖就会出来寻求被咒物的主人
The Lamia will come for the owner of the accursed object.
除非 你不再是主人 你那枚纽扣呢
Unless, of course, you are no longer the owner. Do you have the button?
把它送人 你的诅咒就解除了
Make a gift of it and you've given the curse away.
为何之前你不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me this before?
因为女妖会撕裂你给的那个人的灵魂
Because the Lamia will tear the soul out of whoever you give that to.
他们永世不得超生
They'll burn in hell for eternity.
是我把他们送去的
And I would have sent them there.
我是你的帮凶
And I would be your accomplice.
在天亮之前你要做出决定
Whatever you decide, you have till morning.
好了吗
Is it over?
好了
It's over.
克莱！
Clay!
我咒你下地狱
You will burn in hell!
我咒你下地狱 婊子我咒你下地狱
You will burn in hell! You bitch, you'll burn in hell!
你的死期到了
Your turn's coming!
- 我咒你下地狱  - 还好吗
- You will burn in hell!  - You okay?
见鬼了
Holy shit.
好吧 你确定你还能去圣巴巴拉吗
Okay, you sure you're still okay about the santa barbara trip?
- 是的 我没事  - 真的吗
- Yeah, I'm fine.  - Yeah?
我什么时候接你
And what time should I get you?
我和你在车站碰头吧
It's better if I meet you at the station.
路上我有点事要办
There's something i've gotta do on the way.
我帮你办 来的路上我…
I can do it. You want me to do it on my way to...
不要 我自己能行
No! No. I've got it under control.
- 那么七点半在…  - 啊 我的信封呢
- We'll meet at, like, 7:30 at the...  - Wait! Where's my envelope?
- 什么信封  - 在我钱包里 我刚还拿着的
- What envelope?  - It was in my purse. I just had it!
- 不过是一枚信封  - 不 应该在这里的
- It's just an envelope.  - No, it's gotta be here!
在这呢 终于找到了
It's here, so we'll find it eventually.
- 我的天呀  - 是啊
- Oh, my god.  - Okay.
我以为弄丢了呢 这下好了
I thought I'd lost it. Okay.
再见 七点半 别迟到啦
Bye. 7:30. Don't be late.
爸爸 我们去玩天使游戏好不
Dad, can we go to the angel game?
去看道格队的比赛怎么样
What about the dodgers?
我们只能在城里待几天
We're only gonna be in town for a few days.
我确定要是告诉他我有多在乎你
I'm sure if I just tell him how much I care about you,
他会理解的
I mean, he's gotta understand.
您确定不想要别的吗
Are you sure you don't want anything else?
不要
No.
那你要整晚坐在这儿喝咖啡啊
So you're just gonna sit here drinking coffee all night long.
可能吧 这跟你有什么关系
Yes. Maybe! What's it to you?
美女 我是靠小费赚钱的 喝咖啡的没小费
Honey, I make my money on tips. Coffee drinkers don't tip.
美女
Honey,
只管送咖啡 否则我把这个给你 折磨死你
Just keep the coffee coming or i'll give you a tip you won't forget.
天啊 真是太棒的惊喜了
Oh, my gosh. What a delightful surprise.
你真是世界上最好的人
You're the sweetest person in the world.
以前的事我过往不计 斯图
Never mind what it's about, Stu.
十分钟马上出现 否则我跟经理说
Just get here in 10 minutes or I'm gonna tell mr Jacks
你不想让他知道的事
Something you don't want me to tell him.
是吗 比如说
Oh, yeah? Like what?
第一 从我这偷了麦克弗森贷款文件
Well, for starters, that you stole the Mcpherson loan file off my desk
交给竞争对手 现在你只剩下九分钟
And gave it to First National. Now you got nine minutes!
- 续杯  - 真的吗
- Give me another.  - Seriously?
克莉丝汀 拜托别告发我
Oh, god, Christine, please don't tell on me.
要是被我爸发现了…
I mean, if my dad ever finds out...
- 你想要什么  - 我要给你一件东西
- Just tell me what you want.  - I need to give something to you.
- 一件小礼物  - 礼物？
- A little gift.  - A gift?
我不明白 我以为你叫我到这来
But I don't understand. I thought you called me down here
因为我把贷款交给竞争对手
Because I gave that loan to first national...
你不用明白 闭上你的臭嘴
Look, you don't need to understand. Just shut up!
这份礼物我现在给你 它就是你的东西啦
Now, this gift that I'm giving you, it'll become your property.
你是它的主人 明白吗
You'll be the owner, all right?
明白
Okay.
怎么啦
What?
当我啥也没说
Forget it.
但我想你把它给我 是想了结贷款那事的
But I thought you wanted to give it to me 'cause of the loan Stuff.
走吧
Just leave.
好吧 谢谢你 克莉丝汀
Okay. Thank you so much, Christine.
- 你保证别告诉我爸  - 滚
- But you're not gonna tell my dad, right?  - Go!
好吧
Okay.
谁该下地狱呢
Who does deserve this?
[死亡讣告]
这有可能吗
Well? Is it possible?
有些死者身上会带有吉普赛的咒语
There are gypsy blessings bestowed upon the dead.
他们把礼物送给死者
They give gifts to their departed
来讨好死灵 这样 魂魄得以不灭
To curry favour with the deceased's soul, for, truly, the soul never dies.
对 我相信你可以把诅咒加给一个过世的人
Yes. I do believe you can give the curse to someone who has passed on,
但你必须举行正式的仪式
But you must make a formal gift
把受诅咒的东西作为礼物送给死者
Of the accursed object to the deceased.
我还不止要这么做
I'll do better than that.
我要把它塞进老妖怪的喉咙里
I'll shove it down her goddamn throat!
给她点厉害…
I'm gonna get some...
我把它还给你
I'm giving it back to you!
你要拿好这个
You're gonna take this thing.
你不是要吗
Are you gonna take this thing?
拿着
Take it!
这是你最后一次抓我的头发
That's the last of my hair you're getting!
我克莉丝汀 布朗特此将此受诅的纽扣
I, Christine Brown, do hereby make a formal gift of this button
作为正式的礼物送给西尔维娅·加纳什
To you, Sylvia Ganush!
噎死你 老妖怪
Choke on it, bitch!
再见
Goodbye.
我是克莉丝汀 请留言稍后回您电话
Hi, it's Christine. Leave a message and I'll call you back.
克莉丝汀 我是吉姆 杰克斯
Christine, it's Jim Jim Jacks.
很抱歉这么早打给你
I'm sorry I'm calling so early,
但昨天晚上
But last night,
我发现斯图·鲁宾干得一些坏事
I found some troubling information about our friend Stu rubin.
显然 他偷了你的麦克弗森贷款文件
Apparently, he stole your file on the Mcpherson loan
然后交给竞争对手企图自己捞一笔
And then tried to broker his own deal at first national.
我猜他以为我们没查出来
I guess he thought we wouldn't find out.
本来也没查 但是一小时前
And we wouldn't have either, except that an hour ago,
他到我家 想把所有的过错都归咎于你
He came by my house and tried to pin the whole thing on you.
我戳穿他自相矛盾的谎话之后
After I confronted him about a few inconsistencies in his story,
他就歇斯底里个没完 我就把他炒了
He broke down crying and, well, we won't be seeing him around any more.
我想告诉你一声 周一早上来上班
So I just wanted you to know that, come monday morning,
副经理的位置非你莫属
That assistant manager's position will be waiting for you.
班森乘客
Passenger Benson, please meet your party
请到大厅售票处与队员汇合
At the concourse ticket counter.
- 欢迎来到联合车站  - 要饼干吗 小姐
- Welcome to union station.  - Cookie, miss?
- 不要谢谢  - 我们推荐您
- No, thanks.  - We appreciate you choosing
选择火车作为出行的方式
Train travel as your mode of transportation,
祝您旅途愉快
And we wish you a pleasant journey.
早
Hi. Good morning.
- 不好意思 没开门呢  - 我就想要这大衣
- I'm sorry, we're not open.  - I just... I just want this coat.
我们还没开门
We're not open yet.
我和男友今天的旅程将会非常特殊
My boyfriend and I are taking this really special trip this morning.
拜托
Please?
瑟弗林次 向北途经凡纳伊
Northbound Surfliner, service to Van Nuys,
丝米谷 牛甘松 圣巴巴拉
Simi Valley, Oxnard, Santa Barbara,
- 三路易斯欧比  - 克莱？
- San Luis Obispo...  - Clay?
宝贝抱抱
Hey! Oh, man! Have a body
天啊 真高兴你来了 我有好多话要跟你说
God, I'm so glad you're here. So many things I wanna tell you.
等下 我也有好多话要说
Wait, there's something I wanna say
- 我就直接了当吧  - 好 说吧
- While I have it straight in my head.  - Okay. Go ahead.
你一直都相信我
You never stopped believing in me.
谢谢你
Thank you for that.
还有些事 我以前不承认
And there's something else, something that I couldn't admit to before.
我本可以延长加纳什夫人的贷款 但我没有
I could have given mrs Ganush another extension on her loan, but I didn't.
那是我的主张 是我的错
It was my decision, and it was wrong of me.
你真是好心肠
You have such a good heart.
你真漂亮
You're so beautiful right now.
- 我大衣好看吗  - 好看 真的
- Do you like my new coat?  - I do. I really do.
- 原来那件呢  - 扔了
- What happened to the old one, though?  - I threw it out.
- 我不想再看见它了  - 不
- And I never want to see it again.  - Oh, no.
太糟糕了 因为我在车里…发现了这个
That's too bad, because I... Look what I found. I found this in the car.
我以为…
I thought...
或许你可以…
And I thought maybe you could...
或许你可以把它补回去
I thought maybe you could sew it back on.
我想你拿走了我的收集的特种硬币
And I think you might have my standing liberty quarter,
两个信封一模一样
'Cause the envelopes kind of look the same.
克莉丝 怎么了
Chris, what's wrong?
- 天呢  - 怎么了
- Oh, my god!  - Hey! Hey, hey, hey!
- 天呢  - 小心
停下 克莉丝 天呀
Stop! Chris! Oh, god!
天呢 不要不要不要
Hey! Hey! Hey, hey, no! Hey! Oh, god, no!
不要
Hey, no!
救我
Help me!
救救我
Help me, please!